A Guide to the Papers of James Taylor Ellyson, 1865, 1896-1910
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of James Taylor Ellyson, 1865, 1896-1910
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
4130
This collection consists of ca. 1,500 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These items were given to the University of Virginia Library on January 9, 1953, by J. Taylor Ellyson Crump, of Richmond, Virginia.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of the correspondence and related papers of James Taylor Ellyson (1847-1919), businessman and politician of Richmond, 1865, 1896-1910, ca. 1,500 items (6 Hollinger boxes, 2 linear shelf feet), and contains correspondence, news clippings, financial papers, political papers, Civil War service papers, invitations, and papers pertaining to the 1907 Jamestown Ter-Centennial Exposition.
A list of correspondents writing to Ellyson, with the dates of their letters, is available for this collection beginning on page two. A list of persons to whom Ellyson wrote begins on page 31 of this guide. Topics in the correspondence include: Ellyson's successful campaign for Lieutenant Governor in 1905, the Tennessee Railroad Company, the Old Dominion Building and Loan Association, the Joseph Bryan Memorial Association, the Jefferson Davis Memorial Association, the United Confederate Veterans, Richmond College, the Baptist Church, the Democratic party in Virginia and national politics, Confederate memorial associations, business, and personal affairs.
Ellyson, son of Henry K. and Elizabeth P. Ellyson, attended Columbia College, Richmond College, and the University of Virginia, graduating in 1869 and marrying Lora E. Hotchkiss, also in 1869. During the Civil War, he served in the Confederate army as a member of the 2nd Company of the Richmond Howitzers, surrendering with them at Appomattox and resuming his college work. Following his graduation, he entered into the business world of Richmond, becoming president of the city council, a member of the board of public interests, a state senator, 1885-1888, and served three terms as mayor of Richmond beginning in 1888.
Ellyson was Chairman of the State Democratic Party Committee for twenty-five years, Lt. Governor of Virginia for three terms, 1906-1918, and Governor for the Division of History, Education, and Social Economy for the Jamestown Exposition. He was also on the board of trustees for Richmond College, Chairman of the Richmond city school board, an executive officer of the Education Board of the Baptist General Association of Virginia, President of the State Baptist Association, vice-president of the Southern Baptist Convention, and a representative on the State Mission Board, the Orphanage Board, and Education Board.
Other Descriptive Data
Correspondents Include:
Abell, J.D. (1900 May 2)
Abott, Willis J. (1899 Dec 29)
Adams, Joseph M. (1910 Jun 21)
Ailworth, R. (1908 Jun 1)
Alderman, Edwin Anderson (1906 Jan 29; 1910 Feb 1)
Alcocke, Eleanor R. (1899 Nov 23, Dec 22, Dec 26; 1909 Nov 1, Dec 30; 1910 Feb 2, Feb 16)
Alexander, F. W. ( n.y. May 26)
Allen, G.T. (1909 Aug 24; 1910 Jan 8)
Allison, L.M. (1899 Dec 1)
Amateis, L. (1899 Jul 27)
Amos, Leonard (1909 Sept. 14)
Anderson, A.N. (1899 Dec 29)
Anderson, Byrd (1900 Jan 12)
Anderson, Charles J. (1897 Dec 30; 1906 Apr 18, Apr 27, Dec 6)
Anderson, D.M. (1899 Aug 19)
Anderson, Joseph Berwick (1899 Aug 1; 1900 Jul 31)
Anderson, William Alexander (1899 Nov 4; 1900 Mar 7; 1906 Sept 26; 1910 Jan 13 [2 letters])
Anderson, William E. (1905, Aug 5)
Anderson William T. (1900 Apr 20, Apr 28; 1901 Aug 17)
Angle, Myer (1900 May 7)
Archer, W.S. (1910 Mar 11)
Armstrong, A.B. (1908 Jun 4)
Arnett, Thomas W.W. (1900 Jan 11)
Ashby, Ida W. (1905 Apr 28)
Ashby, James (1905 Jun 30; 1910 Sept 23)
Asher, Mrs. M.H. (1909 Oct 30, Nov 2)
Atkinson, Mrs. H.A. (1909 Sept 13, Sept 25)
Attkinson, A.C. (1896 Dec 7 )
Augell, C. Roy (1909 Aug 12 )
Ba[ ]y, A.E. (1905 Jul 10)
Bacon, Robert (1906 Dec 17)
Bagby, Mrs. John (1909 Apr 19)
Bagby, John Robert (1905 Jul 11)
Bailey, Banks, and Biddle Company (1906 May 2, May 17, May 21, May 26, Jun 7, Nov 22)
Baird, Hugh H. (1905 Jul 15)
Baird, J. Waller (1905 Jul 2)
Baird, William (1905 Jun 30)
Baker, C. [ ] (1906 Dec 21)
Baker, W.W (1909 Sept 21)
Baldwin, W.B. (1900 Mar 7, Mar 12, Jul 17)
Ballard, John N. (1905 Jun 29)
Barham, W.B. (1909 Aug 23)
Baring, Charles (1908 Sept 12)
Barker, J.M. (1905 Jul 14)
Barker, Maggie H. (1909 Jun 18)
Barksdale, William Randolph (1896 Nov 29; 1900 Feb 19, Feb 24)
Barley, Louis C. (1910 Jan 5)
Barnes, Thomas H. (1910 Sept 12)
Barnhardt, J.A. (1910 Feb 10)
Barrett, A.S. (1905 Jun 24)
Batkins, Claude L. (1909 Oct 21)
Baum, A.O. (1905 Jul 1)
Baxter, Garrett (1909 May 21; 1910 Jan 11, Jan 12, Jan 13, Sept 8, Sept 16)
Beazley, R.H. (1900 Jan 23)
Beckham, James M. (1900 Jan 13)
Began, Beeus (1905 Apr 9)
Bell, H.N. (1905 May 19)
Bell, Walton E. (1910 Jan 20)
Bellamy, H.W. (1909 Oct 8)
Berkeley, E. (1909 Mar 30)
Berry, T.J. (1909 Sept 16)
Beverly, Claude F. (1910 Mar 28, Apr 2)
Beverley, Robert (1900 Mar 8)
Bibb, Albert Pendleton (1905 Jun 29)
Bidgood, Joseph N. (1900 Apr 28)
Bird, George T. (1910 Aug 16)
Bishop, E.S. (1899 Nov 22; 1900 Jan 1)
Bitting, William Coleman (1909 Mar 23, May 5)
Black William Murray (1908 Jan 19)
Blacknall, Gladys (1899 Nov 30)
Blanks, James B. (1909 Jun 1, Aug 19, Dec 22)
Blanks, Mrs. W.D. (1910 Feb 12)
Blanton, Wyndham Bolling (1910 Feb 3)
Blick, J.A. (1905 Jul 8)
Bliss, R.A. (1909 Aug 18)
Bloxom, M. Woodson (1899 Aug 29)
Blue, Rupert (1907 Feb 1)
Boardman, Mabel T. (1905 Feb 2; 1910 Jan 7)
Boatwright, F.W. (1899 Aug 26; 1900 Feb 28, Jul 10; 1905 Mar 9; 1909 May 3, Aug 16, Sept 22, Oct 6, Oct 11, Oct 15, Oct 16)
Bohannan, James Gordon (1908 Jun 6)
Boisseau, J.W. (1897 Aug 10)
Bolling, Stith (1906 Dec 6; 1909 Nov 23)
Bolling, Wyndham (1899 Dec 16; 1900 Jan 6, Jan 8, Jan 9; 1909 May 9)
Bonaparte, Charles Joseph (1907 Jan 5)
Bond, W.H. (1906 Oct 30)
Booker, J.E. (1897 Nov 8)
Booker, M.B. (n.d)
Boren, George E. (1899 Sept 25)
Boston, F.R (1909 Oct 15, Oct 29, Dec 21; 1910 Feb 4)
Bowler, Nannie C. (1899 Nov 20)
Bowles, W.I. (1908 Feb 5)
Bowles, William A. (1899 Nov 21)
Bowman, A.M. (1909 Sept 9)
Bowry, C.B (1910 Sept 9)
Boykin, N. Young (1909 Jan 15, Jan 24)
Boykin, R.S. (1905 May 2)
Boykin, Richard E. (1899 Oct 2, Nov 11)
Bradford, F.M. (1905 Jul 5)
Bradley, G.Y. (1909 Jun 28, Sept 25)
Bradley, Herbert Howard (1908 May 6)
Bradley and Company (1907 Aug 29, Sept 2; 1908 Jan 7)
Brauer, Charles E. (1905, Mar 24)
Brauer, Fred C. (1905 Mar 23)
Breen, J.W. (1899 Oct 23, Oct 26; 1909 Nov 15)
Brenaman, Jacob Neff (1896 Dec 5, Dec 21; 1897 Feb 27, Oct 18; 1905 Mar 5)
Brent, R.S. (1905 Jun 29)
Brickey, J.W (1909 Jul 12, Jul 18)
Bridges, H.L (1905 Jun 19)
Bridwell, O.H. (1910 Jan 15)
Brock, R.S. Jr. (1900 Jun 18)
Bronson, Minnie (1906 Sept 12)
Brown, D.A .,Jr. (1909 Apr 20, Jul 13; 1910 Mar 11)
Brown, E.F. (1908 May 25)
Brown, F.A. (1909 Oct 12)
Brown, J.R. (1909 Mar 17)
Brown, John Thompson (1909 Aug 23)
Brown, Mary K. (1910 Mar 21)
Brown, Philip F. (1909 Nov 4)
Brown, W.S. (1908 Feb 3)
Browning, John A. (1900 Jul 2)
Bruce, Philip Alexander (1909 Nov 17)
Bruce, R.P. (1906 Nov 12, n.d.)
Bryan, Belle P. (1910 Mar 18, n.d.)
Bryan, George (1900 May 3)
Bryan, John Steward (1908 Oct 3; 1909 Oct 27)
Bryan, Jonathan (1908 Nov 16; 1909 Apr 13, Apr 15)
Bryan, William Jennings (1906 Oct 3; 1908 Jul 1, Jul 16, Jul 28)
Buchanan, B. F. (1899 Jun 4; 1909 Jan 4)
Buchanan, H.G. (1905 Apr 29)
Buerman, H. (1908 Jan 27, Feb 3)
Buford, A.S. (1906 Feb 23)
Bugham, W.W. (1899 Nov 24)
Burger, John W. (1910 Jan 1)
Burger, W.H. (1899 Sept 7)
Burgess, A.S. (1905 Jun 28)
Burke, F.P. (1908 Jan 24)
Burnett, Charles R. (1908 Aug 26)
Burnley, W.R. (1905 Jul 15)
Burrell, S.C. (1900 Jan 25)
Burrows, H.C. (1910 Feb 18)
Burry, L.S. (1900 Jul 2, Jul 21)
Burton, J. Reginald (1907 Jan, Dec 10, Dec 27; 1908 Jan 7)
Burton, John R. (1909 Nov 6)
Bushby, W. (1907 Sept 16)
Butin, F.R. (1899 Aug 5)
Button, Joseph (1897 Aug 16; 1909 Dec 29)
Byerly, F.A. (1899 Sept 15; 1900 Jul 26)
Byerly, W.A. (1905 Jul 5)
Byrd, R.C. (1900 Mar 7, Mar 12, Jul 17)
Byrd, Richard Evelyn (1909 Aug 21; 1910 Jan 13)
C[ ], W.H. (1905 Jun 6)
Cabell, George C. (n.y. Mar 7)
Cabell, James Alston (1905 Aug 17, Oct 11)
Callahan, Chas H. (1910 Feb 14)
Cameron, George Jr. (1910 Aug 25)
Cameron, William Ewan (1909 Oct 25)
Camp, R.G. (1908 Aug 15)
Camp, R.J. (1900 Apr 14, Apr 26)
Campbell, A.A. (1906 Oct 18, Oct 29, Nov 3; 1907 Nov 15)
Campbell, J. Lawrence (1910 Sept 3)
Campbell, P.M. (1899 Sept 1)
Cannon, James Jr. (1906 May 7)
Caples, R.A. (1908 Sept 8)
Carey, J.D. (1905 Mar 27)
Cargrave, S.C. (1900 Apr 27)
Carlin, Charles Creighton (1909 Mar 20)
Carlton, H.G. (1905 Mar 14)
Carpenter, J.C. (1900 Feb 28)
Carpenter, William W. (1905 Jan 6)
Carper, J.C. (1908 Aug 19)
Carr, Julian Shakespeare (1910, Jan 12)
Carrington, George (1909 Jul 27)
Carrington, J.C. (1908 Jun 9)
Carrington, William H. (1908 Jun 9; 1909 Sept 24; 1910 Aug 28)
Carroll, Charles (1899 Dec 8)
Carroll, P.D. (1900 May 6)
Carson, William Edward (1907 Oct 12)
Carter, William H. Sr. (1910 Sept 29)
Cason, W.W. (1900 Feb 13)
Caton, James Randall (1905 Mar 21, May 19; 1907 Oct 16; 1908 May 4)
Chambers, Frances A. (1909 Apr 14)
Chamblise, John (1909 Feb 14)
Chandler Julian Alvin Carroll (1907 Mar 26, Jun 24; 1909 Jan 26)
Chase, Roland E. (1909 Sept 23)
Chauncey, Charles (1900 Jun 3)
Cheatham, S.J. (1905 Jul 17)
Chesterman, W.D. (1900 Jan 15; 1901 Nov 29)
Chichester, Richard Henry Lee (1907 Oct 21, Oct 25, Oct 30)
Chitwood, Joseph H. (1907 Oct 14)
Chowning, J. William (1909 Jul 28)
Christian, George L. (1907 Nov 21)
Christian, L.T. (1909 Aug 27)
Churhan, George L. (1910 Jul 30)
Clark, Bennie T. (1905 Jul 15)
Clark, Champ (1906 Jan 29)
Clark, T.L. (1906 Oct 22; 1907 Oct 18)
Clarke, Authur B. (1905 Mar 31)
Clarke T.E. (1908 Jun 6)
Claybrook, F.W. (1900 Apr 24)
Coakley, Robert H. (1900 Apr 19)
Cochran, Joseph Wilson (1900 Oct 30)
Cocke, Lucian Howard (1899 Nov 9, Nov 27; 1900 Jan 10)
Cocker, Mrs. Esau (1909 Jun 15)
Cofer, M.J. (1909 Sept 2)
Coffman, Herbert (1900 Jul 27)
Cogbill, Philip Valentine (1900 May 9; 1909 Aug 5)
Coke, John A. (1900 Jan 25)
Coleman, C.R. (1905 Jul 8)
Colhoun, William H. (1900 Jan 17, Mar 8)
Colley, Thomas W. (1905 Jul 10)
Collins, C.T. (1909 Sept 4, Sept 14)
Confederate Publishing Company (1899 Nov 16)
Cooke, George H. (1905 Jul 6)
Cooke, George M. (1905 Apr 29, Aug 8)
Cooke, Merritt T. (1907 Oct 24)
Coone, R.R. (1909 Dec 22)
Cooper, Lawrence (1899 Jul 26)
Cope, Henry Frederick (1909 Nov 3)
Copeland, W.S. (1909 Aug 21, Sept 4, Sept 7)
Core, J.C. (1900 Jan 17)
Corresponding Secretary of the Education Board of the Baptist General Association (1899 Nov 27)
Corvette, R.F. (1905 Jul 10)
Cox, Herbert F. (1899 Jul 27)
Cox, P.A. (1905 Jul 8)
Cox, W.S. (1900 Jul 14)
Cox, William R. (1909 Oct 30)
Crafford, M.W. (1910 Apr 21)
Craft, J.B. (1909 Aug 31)
Crafts, Wilbur F. (1906 May 9)
Cram, Goodhue, and Ferguson Architects (1910 Feb 23)
Creamer, James J. (1905 Mar 29)
Creath, W.T. (1905 Jul 13)
Cree, Thomas K. (1909 Oct 28, Oct 30)
Cridler, Thomas W. (1907 Mar 9, Mar 20, Apr 9, Apr 23 [2 letters], May 18 [2 letters], May 25 [2 letters], May 28 [2 letters], May 30, Jun 4)
Cromwell, A.C. (1910 Jan 23)
Crossman, T.E. (1909 Nov 8)
Crosswell, W.J. (1900 June 11)
Crown, John R. (1909 Jun 10)
Croxton, T.W. (1910 Mar 2)
Crugell, C.R. (1909 Sept 13)
Crump, Frank T. (1905 Jul 18)
Crump, James D. (1899 Sept 11)
Crunden, R.H. (1899 Aug 3)
Cummings, H.J. (1909 Aug 28)
Cunninggim, W.L. (1900 Mar 26)
Curtis, J.C. (1909 Apr 26)
Curtis, J.M. (1905 Apr 28)
Cushen, Ran D. (1905 Jun 29)
Cutchins, C.A. (1899 Dec 4)
Cutchins, John A (1906 Feb 10)
Cutshaw, W.E. (1905 Mar 25)
Dabney, W.T. (1909 Jun 4, Oct 23)
Dalton, M.L. (1910 Sept 28)
Daniel, J.O. (1907 Oct 22)
Daniel, John Warwick (1897 Nov 7; 1899 Sept 23; 1903 Jun 6; 1904 Nov 11; 1908 Jan 11, Jun 16; 1909 Jul 27)
Daniel, William B. (n.d.)
Darst, James H. (1905 Jun 30)
Davenport, Frances G. (1907 Mar 20)
Davies, J. Jenkyn (1900 Jun 22)
d'Aigneau, Eugene (1909 May 28)
Davis, A.W. (1905 Mar 25)
Davis, Chas C. (1900 Feb 13)
Davis, Charles Hall (1900 Dec 20, Dec 27)
Davis, J.G. (1910 Jan 24, Aug 11)
Davis, J.S. (1910 Sept 15)
Davis, S.S. (1905 Jun 10)
Davison, F.B. (1910 Mar 8, Mar 11)
Dawe, G. Grosvenor (1909 Dec 22, Dec 23, Dec 31 [2 letters]; 1910 Jan 20)
Dawes, L.A.(1900 Jun 13)
Day, Charles Fenton (1899 Oct 2, Oct 31; 1908 Jun 4; 1910 Jan 24; Feb 14)
Day, Clement A. (1910 May 28)
Deal, J.T. (1909 May 22)
Dean, William Harper (1905 Apr 10)
de Cordova, Rudolph (1908 Nov 16; 1909 Jan 8, Feb 1)
Deitrick, T.M. (1905 Jul 11 )
Democratic State Chairman (1906 May 22)
Deutzman, Lawrence F. (1910 May 9)
DeVany, George (1899 Aug 1)
DeVault, M.T. (1909 Jan 4, Jan 6, Jan 11, Jan 15, Jan 25, Feb 4, Feb 9, July 10, Sept 8; 1910 Jan 10, Jan 11, Feb 23)
Devier, Giles (1899 Nov 15)
Dew, John G. (1905 Mar 29)
Dictrick [?], V.S. (1905 Jul 8)
Director (1907 Jan 17)
Dobie, Richard A. (1909 Feb 8, 1910 Sept 26)
Dodge, Henry William Jr. (1909 Dec 20)
Dogan, B.J. (1899 Aug 23)
Dowdy, L.S. (1910 Sept 30)
Downing, T.J. (1899 Sept 27)
Drewry Brothers (1900 Mar 2)
Drummond, Thomas H. (1909 Jul 23)
Dudley, Horace L. (1899 Aug 23, Sept 25)
Duke, W.D. (1909 Mar 11, Apr 15, Jun 16, Jul 7, Jul 22, Jul 23, Jul 27, Aug 10, Aug 26, Sept 7, 1909 Oct 14, Nov 13; 1910 Jan 14, Jan 24, Feb 10, Mar 8)
Dunaway, J. Manning (1900 Feb 6)
Dunaway, T.S. (1905 Apr 15, 1909 Sept 14)
Dunlop, John (1900 Jun 15)
Dunlop, R.A. (1899 Sept 30; 1901 Dec 7; 1902 Feb 3; 1909 Mar 12)
Dunn, Elizabeth R. (1909 May 21)
Dupuy, E.L. (1908 Jun 1)
Early, N.B. (1908 Jun 1)
Earp, John I. (1909 Nov 1)
Easley, D.M. (1900 Jul 20)
Echols, Edward (1897 Aug 18, Sept 16; 1905 May 20; 1909 Jul 28)
Eddington, Mrs. Nannie Pegram [Mrs. C.M.] (1909 Nov 2, 16, 24, Dec 28)
Edmonson, H.A. (1908 Jun 2; 1910 Aug 26)
Edmunds, Howard L. (1897 Aug 26; 1900 May 9; 1905 Jun 30)
Edmunds, John R. (1899 Oct 28, Nov 1, Nov 3)
Edwards, J.F. (n.d.)
Edwards, J. Hartwell (1899 Dec 5)
Edwards, William J. (1910 May 5)
Eggleston, J.D. (1909 May 11)
Egleston, Melville (1900 Apr 6, Apr 9, Apr 11, Apr 23, May 4, May 22, Jun 4, Jun 16; 1909 Apr 3)
Ellett, John S. (1900 Jan 1)
Ellett, Thomas (1900 May 21)
Ellington, J.P. (1895, Jun 29)
Ellis, William B. (1908 Sept 28)
Ellison, Charles E. (1910 Mar 8)
Ellyson, Douglas W. (1909 Jan 2)
Ellyson, H. Theodore (1900 Mar 8)
Ellyson, Lizzie W. (1909 Apr 4, Apr 5)
Epes, C.B. (1900 Apr 5)
Epes, Sydney P. (1897 Dec 10, Dec 13)
Evans, H. Tate (1909 Sept 10)
Ewing, Elbert W.R. (1909 Jun 7, Jun 14)
Evans, Clement A. (1905 May 15; 1909 Jun 1)
Fanning, N.O. (1905 Apr 27)
Farmer, James L. (1908 Feb 20)
Farmer, R.E.L. (1909 Sept 10)
Farrand, Thomas H. (1905 Mar 27)
Featherston, Howell C. (1907 Oct 26; 1908 Jul 11)
Featherston, N.R. (1905 Jul 14)
Federation of Mother's Clubs (1910 Jan 28)
Feild, Thomas L. (1908 Oct 27; 1909 Mar 17, Apr 7, Apr 24, Jul 27, Aug 17, Sept 9, Nov 29, Dec 20)
Felden, W.C. (1900 Jul 28)
Ferguson, E. Morris (1899 Aug 30)
Ferguson, S.D. (1900 Jul 12)
Field, D.M. (1907 Mar 24)
Finch, Allen W. (1909 Dec 28)
Finch, Pleasant (1905 Jul 1)
Fishburn, J.B. (1900 Mar 9)
Fisher, T.E. (1908 Jan 31)
Fitzgerald, J.H. (1905 Jul 1)
Fiveash, Joseph G. (1900 Jul 26)
Flanagan, C.A. (1908 May 23)
Fletcher, James H. Jr. (1905 May 25)
Flood, Henry Delaware (1900 Jul 28; 1905 May 1)
Flournoy, H.W. (1899 Nov 27, Nov 29)
Fogle, W.H. (1906 Oct 26)
Folk, William L. (1899 Aug 8)
Folley, Thomas W. (1909 Nov 24)
Forbes, W.S. (1905 Mar 25)
Foster, I.C. (1905 Mar 12)
Foster, J.C. (1905 Apr [?])
Fouchee, William L. (1909 Aug 20)
Found, W.E. (1907 Aug 21)
Francis, H.M. (1907 Jun 8)
Franklin, J. Mack (1909 Jun 3)
Fraser, W.S. (1910 Jan 3)
Freeman, Douglas Southall (1908 Mar 26)
Frost, Arthur Burdett (1908 May 6)
Frost, J.M. (1909 Oct 30)
Frye, B.F. (1899 Sept 30)
Fugate, Henly M. (1900 Jun 15; 1909 Jun 14, Jun 21)
Fuller, Edward R. (1910 Jan 15)
Fuller, Williamson Whitehead (1899 Dec 20, Dec 23)
Funk, A.B. (1905 Jul 1)
Gage, Morton F. (1908 Sept 14)
Gagg, Edward S. (1909 Nov 8)
Gaines, Grenville (1900 May 7; 1909 Nov 6, Nov 30)
Gaines, Rich Venable (1909 Dec 30)
Gainey, S. (1909 Dec 21)
Galeski, S. (1900 Feb 17)
Gallaher, D.C. (1907 Mar 25; 1909 Sept 16)
Galt House Company (1900 May 10)
Ganaway, D.M. (1910 May 11)
Garatt, C.U. (1907 Oct 11)
Garbee, Walter L. (1910 Sept 13)
Gardner, A.P. (1907 Jan 11, Jan 22, Jan 24)
Gardner, J.S. (1905 Apr 17)
Garland, M.H. (1905 Jun 28)
Garnett, H.T. (1899 Oct 25; 1907 Dec 3)
Garnett, James Mercer (1909 Jan 12)
Garnett, Theodore S. (1909 Jun 1)
Garrett, B.C. (1900 Mar 30)
Garrett, John D. (1900 Feb 17)
Garrett, William Allen (1908 Jun 5; 1910 Aug 31)
Garrett, W.T. (1910 Jan 18)
Garth, B. Gates (1905 Jun 28)
Genealogical Publishing Company (1910 Jan 31)
Gessler, Theodore A.K. (1900 Apr 6, Apr 23)
Getz, W.J. (1905 Jul 5)
Gilbert, M.R. (1907 Mar 3)
Giles, J.E. (1905 Jul 17)
Gilkeson, Hansford G. (1910 Jan 10)
Gillette, J.L. (1905 Mar 13)
Gilliam, Robert (1908 Jun 6; 1909 Dec 29; 1910 Jan 24)
Glasgow, Joseph A. (1908 Jun 1)
Gleaves, C.W. (1900 Apr 19)
Goad, E.V. (1909 Aug 30)
Godoy, Jose Francisco (1909 Jul 12)
Goerly [?], W.H. (1900 Feb 16)
Goff, Edward L.C. (1908 Sept 29)
Goffigan, William E. (1907 Oct 14)
Gold, Thomas Daniel (1910 Feb 14)
Gooch, W.S. (1910 Jan 6)
Goode, John K. (1900 Mar 27)
Goodman, Thomas F. (1908 Jul 7)
Goodwin, P.E. (1909 May 10)
Goodwin, Miss Rosa P. (1909 Mar 10)
Goolrick, C. O'Conor (1907 Oct 14)
Goolrick, John T. (1909 Sept 11)
Gordon, Armistead Churchill (1899 Sept 30)
Gordon, Bennett T. (1910 Aug 27)
Gordon, Reuben Lindsay (1899 Oct 27)
Gordon, J.B. (1903 May 9)
Gordon, William B. (1910 Mar 5)
Gouldman, G.J. (1899 Oct 25, Oct 28)
Gravatt, Charles U. (1910 Aug 28)
Gray, A.A. (1905 Jul 14)
Gray, J.B. (1905 Apr 18)
Gray, R.T. (1899 Dec 29)
Graybill, Michael (1905 Jul 6)
Grayson, E.C. (1905 Jun 30)
Green, Anne S. (1909 Jan 13)
Green, E.A. (1899 Sept 6)
Green, M.M. (1908 Jun 7)
Green, Raleigh T. (1909 Aug 16; 1910 Jan 8)
Green, W.E. (1899 Jul 29)
Greenberg, Harry (1909 Jun 28)
Greene, George O. (1909 May 20)
Gregory, George E. (1905 Mar 29)
Gregory, J.D. (1905 Aug 18)
Gregory, J.M. (1910 Sept 15)
Gregory, Oliver Fuller (1909 Jun 15)
Griffin, John T. (1910 Jan 31)
Griffin, Percy (1899 Nov 8)
Grigg, J.A. (1905 Mar 16)
Griggs, A. McK. (1900 Jan 29)
Gruar, C.W. (1905 Jul 10)
Gwaltney, Leslie (1899 Sept 8)
Haas, Talfourd N. (1900 Jun 21)
Hadley, [ ] James S. (1909 May 22)
Hadwellavlin, J. (1905 Jun 30)
Haines, Charles W. (1897 Oct 15)
Hall A. S. (1907 Oct. 25)
Hall, Mrs. V.E. (1907 Dec 12)
Hall, William (1899 Nov 15)
Hallen, R.G. (1905 Jun 29)
Halsey, Don Peters (1905 Oct 27; 1909 Dec 24)
Hamersly, L.R. (1909 Nov 8)
Hamilton, R.P. (1908 Dec)
Hanckel & Hanckel (1905 Apr 27)
Hannah, J.K. (1910 Sept 7)
Hardenbrook, William Ten Eyck (1910 Jan 13, Jan 20, Jan 31, Mar 2)
Hardwick, James T. (1900 Mar 9)
Harlow, M.B. (1909 Apr 21, Jul 19; 1910 Feb 5)
Harper, Fred (1905 Apr 29)
Harper, J.W. (1905 Apr 27)
Harris, R.T. (1905 Jun 31)
Harris, T.S. (1905 Jun 29)
Harris, W.A. (1909 Dec 31)
Harris, Walter Edward (1905 Mar 8)
Harrison, J.T. (1900 Apr 14)
Harrison, Randolph (1899 Oct 26)
Hart, John M. (1907 Oct 11)
Harvey, E. G. (1905, Jul 7)
Harwood, James C. (1900 Mar 30)
Hasbrook, Albert E. (1900 Jul 10)
Haseman, Evelyn I. (1909 Feb 8)
Hash, Walter A. (1909 Feb 16, Sept 9, Nov 3)
Haskins, Meade (1987 Nov 6)
Hatcher, Mrs. W.E. (1910 Jan 13)
Hatcher, William E. (1905 Mar 16; 1908 Aug 28)
Hawkins, O.A. (1910 Sept 26)
Hawkins, Steele A. (1909 Jun 15)
Hay, James (1899 Dec 6; 1900 Mar 12, May 22; 1905 May 1, Jul 17; 1910 Aug 23)
Hayden, George H. (1910 Jan 10, Jan 13)
Hayes, J.A. (1909 Oct 9, Oct 18, Oct 19, Oct 25)
Haynes, Mrs. Andrew (1909 Mar 26)
Hazard, Carleton B. (1909 Jan 7)
Heindl, Paul A. (1905 Apr 1)
Heinz, Mrs. W.J. (1897 Oct 14)
Heitmuller, Anton (1909 Jul 24)
Hemphill, J.C. (1910 Jan 20)
Henderson, Frank K. (1909 Sept 4)
Henderson, J.T. (1909 Aug 23, Sept 2, Sept 27)
Henefer, George (1899 Nov 6)
Hanritz, T.L. (1900 Jan 6)
Henry, Albert M. (1908 Dec 29)
Henry, R.R. (1897 Oct 20)
Herndon, R.H. (1909 Sept 1)
Herring, B.C. (1909 Jan 5)
Heth, Nannie Randolph (1909 Sept 16; 1910 Feb 6)
Heth, Stockton (1905 Apr 17)
Hickey, John M. (1908 Jun 1)
Hicks, Jesse G. (1905 Mar 29)
Hicks, Robert C. (1910 Jan 28)
Higgins, Daniel (1905 Mar 27)
Hiles, P.T. (1905 May 2)
Hill, A.H. (1909 Mar 1)
Hill, David B. (1900 Jul 12)
Hill, R.D. (1905 Jul 10)
Hill, R.T. (1900 Jan 25)
Hillard, Charles H. (1899 Aug 24)
Hilton, William Paul (1908 Oct 13; 1909 May 1)
Hinds and Noble, Publishers, New York (1909 Sept 25)
Hines, T.A. (1909 Nov 6)
Hix, William Daniel (1900 Jan 31; 1907 May 30)
Hobbs, Alex R. (1908 Jun 4)
Hobbs, Stella B. (1910 Aug 13)
Hobe, F.S. (1908 Jun 1)
Hobson, J. Haskins (1905 Mar 14)
Hobson, Richmond Pearson (1907 Apr 1)
Hobson W.N. (1905 Jun 30)
Hodges, William Thomas (1910 Sept 10)
Hogg, W.F. (1905 Jun 28)
Holcomb, A.N. (1910 Feb 1, Feb 15)
Holen, C.F. (1897 Oct 21)
Holland, Alfred (1899 Jul 28)
Holland, Edward E. (1907 Oct 11; 1910 Aug 26)
Holland, J. Peter (1905 Jul 10)
Holman, W.W. (1905 May 1)
Holt, Henry W. (1910 Sept 2)
Hooker, J.M. (1910 Sept 30)
Hoover, M.J. (1909 Nov 3)
Hopkins, J.S. (1905 Jul 1)
Horetey, R.B. (1905 Jun 29)
Hornor, John J. (1900 Jul 5, Jul 12)
Horsley, Kathryn W. (n.d.)
Hosier, J. Walter (1899 Nov 11, Dec 6)
Hotchkiss, Jedediah (1897Aug 17)
Hotel Ponce de Leon (1908 Apr 1, Apr 3)
Houley, John (1896 Dec 5)
Houston, Harry R. (1909 Dec)
Howard, A.M. (1899 Sept 27)
Howard, Francis (1907 Mar 9, Mar 20, May 7; 1908 Dec 15)
Howard, Roy W. (1907 Nov 29)
Howle, W.E. (1907 Oct 17)
Hubard, Edmund Wilcox (1899 Nov 15)
Hudgin, J.M. (1897 Oct 25)
Hudgins, H.H. (1909 Nov 10)
Huffman, O.L. (1908 Jun 1)
Hughes, Floyd (1907 Mar 20)
Hudges, Robert Morton (1909 Mar 2)
Hume, Thomas (1910 Apr 24)
Humphreys, Henry O. (1900 May 5; 1909 Nov 18, Dec 29)
Hundley, George Jefferson (1896 Nov 30)
Hunton, Eppa Jr. (1905 Mar 13)
Hurst, Sam N. (1910 May 9)
Hutcheson, H.F. (1905 May 20, Jun 30)
Hutchison, F.M. (1905 Apr 17)
Hutzler, Charles (1908 Dec 2)
Hutzler, Henry S. (1909 Mar 9)
Hyatt, J. Hallett 1906 Oct 6, Oct 13 (1907 Jan 27, Feb 15, Feb 23, Feb 27 [2 letters], Mar 6, Mar 9, Mar 13, Mar 18, Mar 28, Apr 18, May 1, Jun 6, Jun 24, Jul 25, Oct 8, Dec 16)
(1908 Jan 10, Jan 27, May 2, May 7, May 13, May 23)
1909 Mar 30, Apr 6, May 29 Hyde, Tristram T. (1909 Jul 14, Jul 23)
Ingleby, Holcolm (1907 Apr 14, Apr 16; 1909 Jan 26)
Irvine, Robert Tate (1900 Mar 7, Apr 10; 1905 Jul 13; 1909 Nov 8)
Jackson, E.B. (1899 Aug 5)
Jakeman, G.M. (1905 Jul 17)
James, Charles E. (1909 Jan 22)
James Rorer Anderson (1897 Oct 20)
James Walter Belknap (1899 Jul 26)
Jamison, Mrs. John J. (1899 Sept 25)
Jamison, T.E. (1905 Jul 5)
Janney, Tyson (1907 Oct 11)
Jeffrey, Lee M. (1900 Jul 16)
Jenkins, E.C. (1909 Nov 8)
Jennings, C.H. (1897 Nov 3)
Jennings, George B. (1899 Dec 23)
Jennings, Tipton D. (1909 Dec)
Jimett, J.A. (1905 May 4)
Johnson, B.F. Publishing Company (1899 Nov 18, Nov 24; 1900 Mar 19)
Johnson, Conway R. (1900 Jun 21)
Johnson, Henry and Sons and Company, Inc. (1907 Dec 24)
Johnson, J.D. (1899 Nov 21)
Johnson, J.G. (1900 Jun 3, Jun 22)
Johnson, J. Jeter (1899 Aug 21)
Johnson, Mrs. J. Massie (1909 Aug 5)
Johnson, Margaret Walker (1909 Aug 18)
Johnson W.W. (1905 Mar 24)
Johnston, C.A (1908 Jun 3)
Johnston, C. Brooks (1907 Mar 13)
Johnston, David E. (1900 Jan 9, Jun 14)
Jones, C.E. (1909 Sept 7)
Jones, Charles A. (1905 Jul 12)
Jones, Clagett Bennet (1897 Oct 27; 1900 Apr 20)
Jones, F. Harper (1897 Oct 18)
Jones, Fred (1909 Dec 29)
Jones, Feeman W. (1910 Sept 17)
Jones, J.C. (1905 Jul 1)
Jones, J.J. (1908 Jun 29)
Jones, J. William (1905 Apr 26; 1908 Jul 10)
Jones, James K. (1900 Feb 26, May 9)
Jones, Joseph J. (1909 Apr 7, Apr 16, May 3)
Jones, M. Ashby (1900 Mar 23)